Guide to the Metropolitan Council on Housing Records TAM.173
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. Subject Files, 1961-1992; 85275; 14 Linear Feet
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85466 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85465 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85464 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85463 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85462 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85461 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85460 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85459 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85458 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85457 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85456 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85455 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85454 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85453 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85452 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85451 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85450 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85449 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85448 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85447 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85446 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85445 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85444 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85443 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85442 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85441 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85440 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85439 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Mitchell-Lama: includes files on developments, 1976-1982; 85438 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Mobilization Against Displacement, 1981; 85437 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Mobilization for Youth, undated; 85436 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Model Cities, undated; 85435 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Model Cities, undated; 85434 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Modular Housing, undated; 85433 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Mollen, Scott, undated; 85432 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Moynihan, Daniel, undated; 85431 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - National Tenants Organization, undated; 85430 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - National Tenants Organization, undated; 85429 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - National Tenants Organization, undated; 85428 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - National Tenants Organization, undated; 85427 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - National Tenants Organization, undated; 85426 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - National Tenants Rights Project, undated; 85425 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - National Tenants Union, undated; 85424 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Save Our Homes Committee, undated; 85423 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - NY State Legislation Coalition, undated; 85422 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - NY State Tenants Organization, undated; 85421 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - No Heat No Rent Committee, undated; 85420 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 104-76, undated; 85419 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85418 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85417 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85416 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85415 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85414 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85413 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85412 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85411 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85410 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Public Housing, undated; 85409 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85408 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85407 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85406 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85405 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85404 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85403 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85402 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85401 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85400 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85399 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85398 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85397 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85396 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85395 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85394 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Public Housing: specific developments and years, undated; 85393 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Riverside Edgecomb Neighborhood Association (RENA), undated; 85392 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Receivership, undated; 85391 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Rent Control (City), 1971-1975; 85390 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Rent Control (City), 1971-1975; 85389 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Rent Control (City), 1971-1975; 85388 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Rent Control (City), 1971-1975; 85387 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85386 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85385 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85384 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85383 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85382 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85381 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85380 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85379 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85378 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85377 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85376 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85375 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85374 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Rent Control (City), 1967-1971; 85373 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Rent Control (City), 1961-1967; 85372 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Rent Control (City), 1961-1967; 85371 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Rent Control (City), 1961-1967; 85370 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rent Control (City), 1961-1967; 85369 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rent Control (City), 1961-1967; 85368 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Rent Control - Vacancy Decontrol, undated; 85367 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Rent Control - Vacancy Decontrol, undated; 85366 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Rent Controls, 1975-1976; 85365 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Rent Controls, 1975-1976; 85364 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rent Controls, 1975-1976; 85363 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Rent Controls, 1975-1976; 85362 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Rent Controls, 1975-1976; 85361 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85360 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85359 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85358 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85357 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85356 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85355 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85354 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Rent Stabilization, undated; 85353 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Rent Stabilization, undated; 85352 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rent Stabilization, undated; 85351 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Rent Control: Maximum Base Rent (MBR), undated; 85350 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Rent Control: Maximum Base Rent (MBR), undated; 85349 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85348 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85347 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85346 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85345 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Rent Control (various topics), undated; 85344 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1980-1982; 85343 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1980-1982; 85342 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1980-1982; 85341 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1980-1982; 85340 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1980-1982; 85339 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85338 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85337 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85336 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85335 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85334 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85333 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85332 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85331 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85330 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85329 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85328 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85327 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85326 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978- 1987; 85325 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85324 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85323 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1978-1987; 85322 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1983-1986; 85321 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1983-1986; 85320 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1983-1986; 85319 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1983-1986; 85318 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1983-1986; 85317 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Tenant Unity Coalition, 1987; 85316 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Tenant Unity Coalition, 1988-1989; 85315 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Tenant Unity Day, 1979; 85314 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Tenant Unity Day, 1980; 85313 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Tenant Unity Day, 1981; 85312 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Tenant Unity Day, 1988; 85311 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Tenant Unity Day, 1989; 85310 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Tenants Political Action Committee (TEN PAC), undated; 85309 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Tenants Power, undated; 85308 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Tenant Survival Conference, 1979; 85307 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Tenant Teams for Action, undated; 85306 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Tenants Union of the Lower East Side, undated; 85305 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Tenants United for Affordable Housing (TUFA), undated; 85304 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Third Avenue Coalition, undated; 85303 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Tompkins Square, undated; 85302 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Tudor City Tenant Association., undated; 85301 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Unaffiliated Columbia Tenants Organization, undated; 85300 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - United Public Housing Assn. Of Yonkers, undated; 85299 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Unity Party 1983, undated; 85298 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Unity Party 1982-3 #1, undated; 85297 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Unity Party 1982 #2, undated; 85296 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Unity Party 1981 (see also Barbaro), undated; 85295 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Uptown Tenants Council, undated; 85294 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Site 30, undated; 85293 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Urban Renewal 1989, 1990, 1991, 1992, undated; 85292 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Urban Renewal-NYC #1, undated; 85291 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Urban Renewal-NYC #2, undated; 85290 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Urban Renewal-NYC #3, undated; 85289 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Urban Renewal 1976 #4, undated; 85288 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Urban Renewal and Public Housing Panel, undated; 85287 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam, undated; 85286 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Warehousing, undated; 85285 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Warehousing, 1991; 85284 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Warehousing, 1990; 85283 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Warehousing, 1989; 85282 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Warehousing, 1988; 85281 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Warehousing, 1987; 85280 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Warranty of Habitability #1 (Milano Decision), undated; 85279 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Warranty of Habitability #2, undated; 85278 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Washington Heights Tenants Association and Citizens Committee of Washington Heights, undated; 85277 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Washington Square, undated; 85276 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Series III. 2002 through 2007 Accretions, 1939-1999; 84792; 22 Linear Feet
  This series contains subject and administrative files relating to the themes covered in Series I and II, and files on Met Council's radio program on WBAI, including audiocassettes of interviews, MCH branch and building organizations and other tenant organizations, including the Cooper Square Committee, East Side Tenants Council, and the Riverside Edgecombe Neighborhood Association, the Neighborhood Preservation Program, squatters, files about Jane Benedict and Esther Rand, and some Spanish language tenant materials. Box 27 consists solely of Audio/Visual materials.
  - East Side Tenants Council record book (1963)East Side Tenants Council files (late 1970s/early 1980s), 1963, 1970s-1980s; 85274 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Rent Guidelines Board (RGB)/Rent stabilization, MCH's work on, 1981; 85273 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Housing Court, MCH's work on, 1973, 1975-1976, 1979; 85272 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Housing Court, MCH's work on, 1984-1985, 1987; 85271 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Squatters, 1970; 85270 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - MCH on Public Housing, undated; 85269 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Bronx Branch, undated; 85268 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Harlem Branch, undated; 85267 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Queens Branch, undated; 85266 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - West Side Branch, undated; 85265 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - West Side Coalition, undated; 85264 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Midtown Branch, undated; 85263 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - West Village Urban Renewal, 1961; 85262 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - MCH Urban Renewal, 1961; 85261 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with Wagner on rent control, 1963; 85260 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Rent control battle, 1963; 85259 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Price control materials, 1940s; 85258 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Daily Compass articles on housing and rent control, 1949; 85257 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Articles on housing, 1940s-1950s; 85256 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - American Labor Party materials on rent and housing, 1950s; 85255 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Leaflets, undated; 85254 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Committee to end discrimination in Stuytown pamphlet, 1940s-1950s; 85253 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - NY tenant councils, 1949; 85252 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - West Side Tenant and Consumer Council, undated; 85251 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Tenant Guides, 1939, 1947; 85250 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Symposium, 1962; 85249 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Lower East Side newsletter, 1966; 85248 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Committee, 1963-1964; 85247 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Albany and City Hall lobbying - Frances Goldin, committee chair, undated; 85246 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - MCH minutes and materials, 1959; 85245 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Vacant lot and building survey, for book A Citizen's Guide to…, 1964; 85244 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Cooper Square, 1960s; 85243 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper clippings and reader survey, 1961; 85242 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1950s-1960s; 85241 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Lower East Side branch: includes Stalling campaign, 1980s; 85240 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Letters, minutes, 1963; 85239 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - 178 East 2nd Street (MCH-organized building, in news), 1974; 85238 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - MCH and Civilian Review Board, 1964; 85237 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Annual conference "Press Panel", 1965; 85236 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - East Side Tenants Council (Part of MCH), 1950s; 85235 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Rent control amendment hearings, 1964; 85234 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Urban renewal projects (adopted) (Esther Rand's files: letters, clippings, statements), 1960-1962; 85233 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Urban renewal sites (dropped) (Esther Rand's file), 1960; 85232 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - East Side Tenants Council (Esther Rand's file), 1960; 85231 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - NAACP (Esther Rand's file), undated; 85230 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - MCH minutes and memoranda (Esther Rand's file), undated; 85229 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - East Side papers of Esther Rand and Frances Goldin, 1960s; 85228 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous MCH, 1960s; 85227 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Habitat Forum NYC (Esther Rand), 1975; 85226 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - NY State Tenants and Neighbors, undated; 85225 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - NY State Tenants and Neighbors, undated; 85224 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - NY State Tenants and Neighbors, undated; 85223 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - NY State Tenants and Neighbors, undated; 85222 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - NY State Tenants and Neighbors, undated; 85221 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Tenants March on Gracie Mansion, 1970; 85220 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - NY State Commission to Study Rents, 1977-1980; 85219 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Unity Party (Jane Benedict candidate for governor), 1982; 85218 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Tenants Union, undated; 85217 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - National Tenants Union, undated; 85216 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Rent Control Lobbying, 1961; 85215 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Rent Control Lobbying, 1961; 85214 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Frances Goldin correspondence, conference programs and flyers, studies etc., 1963-1964; 85213 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Early MCH urban renewal fights, undated; 85212 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - MCH publications: fact sheets, booklets, manuals, 1960s-1970s; 85211 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - MCH publications: fact sheets, booklets, manuals, 1960s-1970s; 85210 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Tenant News, 1962-1965; 85209 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - MCH and antipoverty programs, 1967; 85208 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Frances Goldin: correspondence with Roger Start, Councilman Katzman, photo in NY Times, letters-to-the-editor, 1961-1968; 85207 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - MCH minutes, drafts, and memos, 1958-1960s; 85206 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Organized Tenants, Inc., 1962; 85205 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Citywide Council for Better Housing: Jane Benedict, member, Caroline Roest, secretary, 1957; 85204 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - MCH Trade Union Committee, 1983-1984; 85203 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - WLIB radio show air tests Interviews with organizers of other organizations: Tony Aguilar, Terry Mizrahi, Rima McKay, Mary Daily (NWBCCC), Apr 13, 1993, undated; 85201; 5 audiocassettes (Box 27, Cassette 1-5)
  - CB #3 Meeting Grand Street Settlement, 1993 May 18; 582340; 5 audiocassettes (Box 27, Cassette 6-10)
  - Orfeo Negro/O Samba, undated; 582341; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing Conference on Public Domain Workshop on Financing, Nov 22, 1975; 582342; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing Workshop II Conference. Includes Mamie J., Esther Rand, and Thomas Foscolis, Nov 22, 1975; 582349; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Speak Out WHN 105 AM Klein Sulzberger, Susan Cohen, P. Hanley, Jun 9, 1974; 582343; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Roger Hayes, May 29, 1995; 582344; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Arlene Frances with Jane Benedict and Lester Evans WDR-AM 710 1:15 PM, Feb 2, 1972; 582345; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Jane B. Arlene Frances show, Apr 1996; 582352; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Where Have All the Neighborhoods Gone Part II, 1984; 582354; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - J.B. and Keith Johnson Suburban Action Inst. WBLS 7:00 AM and J.B. Mattie Gittens (Sea Rise) WBLS 7:00 AM, Dec 2, 1979 and Dec 9, 1979; 582355; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Jane Benedict WABC TV. JB.'s last words "We now come to vacancy decontrol" and Esther Rand on WBAI (by timeclock), Feb 1971, 1971; 582356; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Jane Benedict Channel 2 CBS 7:30 PM Dave Marash "Eye On" Includes Ferrentino, Moses (chip), Sulzberger, A. Kerr and Weiner, Oct 13, 1973; 582357; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - WBLS J.B. and Councilman Gilberto Gerera Valentin to 430 and Arlene Frances WOR with Jane Benedict and WM Moses, C.H.I.P., May 21, 1978 and Jun 1, 1978; 582358; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Jane Benedict-Patricia McCann Show WOR-AM 710, Jan 14, 1972; 582359; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing Program WBLS J.B. and Councilman Fred Samuel 8:00 AM and WBLS J.B. and Roth Steele, Jun 18, 1978 and Jun 25, 1978; 582360; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - J.B. and Bess Stevenson WBLS and J.B. and Senator McColl WBLS 8:00 AM, Jul 2, 1978 and Jul 9, 1978; 582361; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Jane Benedict and Robert Morrero WBLS, Jun 4, 1978 and Jun 11, 1978; 582362; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Jane Benedict WMCA 11:15 AM John Hamberg Show, Dec 6, 1974; 582363; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - J.B. and Bob Morrero WBLS; J.B. and Birdwell; J.B. and Mehitina Selassi, Apr 9, 1978, Apr 16, 1978, Apr 23, 1978; 582364; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Hawley (rehearsals) Point of View WQXR 6:30 PM and Jane Benedict with Steve Powers WHN 1050 11:30 PM, Oct 11, 1974 and Nov 10, 1974; 582365; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - WOR Radio 710 AM Arlene Francis Show with Diane Lambert Robert Greene, and Jane Benedict 1:15 PM, Aug 14, 1974; 582372; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - J.B. and Bess Stevenson WLIB; J.B. and Leah Williams WLIB; Sam Hall Program WNBC; J.B. and Betty Hocke of Operation Open City, Apr 30, 1978, May 7, 1978, May 7, 1978, May 14, 1978; 582366; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - [RGB] with Ken Rosenfelt Leslie Holmer, Jun 13, 1995; 582367; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - J.B. and Major Owens WBLS and J.B. and Robert Morrero WBLS, Mar 28, 1978 and Apr 2, 1978; 582368; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - [unidentified cassette tape], undated; 582369; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - WBLS J.B. and Bess Stevenson and Metropolitan Council on Housing J.B. and Robert Morrero WLIB, Mar 12, 1978 and Feb 26, 1978; 582371; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival. Reagan and Rent Controls Bob Morrero Jane Benedict; Barbara [Braelle], [Jim Read], and Jane Benedict, Lakeview, Dec 7, 1980 and Dec 14; 582370; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Tenants Fight For Survival. Guest: Ruth Steel Topic: Mitchalama housing, Mar 5, 1978; 582346; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival WBLS-FM 107.5 8:00 AM Host: Jane Benedict Guest: Esther Rand, Mar 19, 1978; 582347; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival WBLS-FM 8:00 AM Hostess: Jane Benedict Guest: Esther Rand/ Eng. Pat Johnson 30 minutes, May 28, 1978; 582348; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Esther Rand (30 minutes), undated; 582350; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Building Opening Ceremony 71 East 4th Street, Aug 28, 1991; 582353; 1 audiocassette (Box 27)
  - Lincoln Swados, undated; 582373; 2 videocassettes (Box 27)
  - Housing Crimes Trial Reel #6, Dec 6, 1970 and Oct 13, 1971; 582374 (Box TAM Shared Access Box 1, Box 27)
  - Housing Crimes Trial Reel #7, Dec 6, 1970 and Oct 13, 1971; 582976 (Box 27, Box TAM Shared Access Box 1)